<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?><rss version="2.0"
	xmlns:content="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/content/"
	xmlns:wfw="http://wellformedweb.org/CommentAPI/"
	xmlns:dc="http://purl.org/dc/elements/1.1/"
	xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"
	xmlns:sy="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/syndication/"
	xmlns:slash="http://purl.org/rss/1.0/modules/slash/"
	>

<channel>
	<title>Education &#8211; Don Bosco Technical High School</title>
	<atom:link href="https://biz-zle.github.io/donbosco/category/education/feed/" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
	<link>https://biz-zle.github.io/donbosco</link>
	<description></description>
	<lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 16:38:46 +0000</lastBuildDate>
	<language>en-US</language>
	<sy:updatePeriod>
	hourly	</sy:updatePeriod>
	<sy:updateFrequency>
	1	</sy:updateFrequency>
	<generator>https://wordpress.org/?v=6.3.2</generator>
	<item>
		<title>Bachelor of Art &#038; Science</title>
		<link>https://biz-zle.github.io/donbosco/bachelor-of-art-science/</link>
					<comments>https://biz-zle.github.io/donbosco/bachelor-of-art-science/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[dbths]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 16:38:46 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://biz-zle.github.io/donbosco/2021/09/19/bachelor-of-art-science/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Bachelor of Arts from the bachelor&#8217;s degree awarded for an undergraduate program in the arts. A Bachelor of Arts degree course is generally completed in three or four years, depending on the country and [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>B</strong>achelor of Arts<strong> </strong>from the bachelor&#8217;s degree awarded for an undergraduate program in the arts. A Bachelor of Arts degree course is generally completed in three or four years, depending on the country and institution.</p>



<p>In colleges and universities in Australia, New Zealand, Nepal, and South Africa, the BA degree can be taken over three years of full-time study. Students must pursue at least one area of study and units from that subject are usually studied in each year, though sometimes students may choose to complete upper-level classes in the same year and as a result, can leave space for elective subjects from a different field. At some universities, students may choose to pursue a second major; alternatively, the remainder of the degree is taken up with a minor area of study (in the first two years) and other individual or stream-based subjects. Honors is an additional year of study after the BA degree, that combines aspects of undergraduate study with those of postgraduate research. Entry to the honors program is usually highly selective.</p>



<p>Education in Canada is controlled by the provinces and can be very different depending on the province. Canadian universities typically offer four-year Bachelor of Arts degrees. In many universities and colleges, Bachelor of Arts degrees are differentiated either as BA or as honors BA degrees. Honor is an academic distinction indicating that a student achieved their BA degree with a sufficiently high overall grade point average; in addition, some programs may require more education than non-honors programs.</p>



<p>In the Netherlands, the BA and Master of Arts (MA) degrees were introduced in 2002. Until then, a single program led to the degree, which comprised the same course load as the bachelor&#8217;s and master&#8217;s programs combined. The title <em>doctorandus</em> was used in almost all fields of study; other titles were used for legal studies (<em>meester</em>, Dutch for master, abbreviated <em>Mr.</em>) and engineering  Those who had already started the <em>doctorandus</em> program could, on completing it, opt for the <em>doctorandus</em> degree (entitling them to use &#8220;Drs.&#8221; in front of their name) or could use the master&#8217;s degree (postnominal letters) in accordance with the new standard.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p><em>The needs of a small-time tour operator are a lot different from the needs of a large international travel agency itself.</em></p><p><strong>Steve Doe –&nbsp;</strong>Partner</p></blockquote>



<hr class="wp-block-separator"/>



<p>Eventually, you must also offer them attractive and competitive tour packages. You must be able to clearly communicate to your customers what your services are, how they are different from others compelling manner.</p>



<p>Of course, you would want your visitors to conveniently reach out to you and contact you. You would want to display all the crucial information about your company, including a map that would show your visitors where exactly they will find you.</p>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading">Displaying Company Information</h5>



<p>Here are the major fear of rejection symptoms identified by psychologists:</p>



<ul><li>It’s all the better if you can accept payments online so that you can close the sales then and there.</li><li>It is much easier and convenient for your customers as well, and you too increase your chance of generating leads.</li><li>To make sure that your travel company website is compatible with some kind of online payment mechanism.</li><li>These will be crucial and highly beneficial for you later in the process.</li></ul>



<h1 class="wp-block-heading">H1: Reject the Fulfilling Prophecy</h1>



<p>This is my average total monthly spending from one year living in Seattle’s Capitol Hill, one year living in San Francisco’s Upper Haight, one year traveling to 20 countries, and one month at a hotel in Bali. It is much cheaper for me to travel. Since the majority of my costs are from trains and flights, it’s significantly cheaper if I stay in one place.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">H2:Focus On How You Want to Be</h2>



<p>This is my average total monthly spending from one year living in Seattle’s Capitol Hill, one year living in San Francisco’s Upper Haight, one year traveling to 20 countries, and one month at a hotel in Bali. It is much cheaper for me to travel. Since the majority of my costs are from trains and flights.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">H3: Construct a Narrative</h3>



<p>Instead of working during the daylight hours and pushing all my free time to the worst part of the day, I prefer to enjoy the days and work at night. I get out of bed faster when I’m excited to go out, and when I don’t have to commute there’s just more time in the day. I like to work 7 days a week with flexible hours so I can take a day off when I please or enjoy an empty movie theater at 2pm.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">H4: Tap Into Your Imagination</h4>



<p>I now have friends all over the world whose life experiences are very different than mine and bring fresh perspectives to my ideas. I’m learning about the real problems that affect the world on a global scale, which will make me.</p>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading">H5: Embrace Not Knowing</h5>



<p>There’s a growing community of “digital nomads” who live a location independent lifestyle. We’re software developers, designers, writers, journalists, engineers, and all sorts of people who share a passion for the work we do.</p>



<h6 class="wp-block-heading">H6: Remember You Will Survive</h6>



<p>Three years ago I was preparing to leave my job at Microsoft to move to San Francisco to start a startup. My friend asked me “but why do you need to be in San Francisco when you can work on a computer from anywhere?” His question made a lot of sense. As I thought about it more, I began to question my assumptions about a “normal life” which don’t make sense in our modern world.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://biz-zle.github.io/donbosco/bachelor-of-art-science/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Master Of Computer Science</title>
		<link>https://biz-zle.github.io/donbosco/master-of-computer-science/</link>
					<comments>https://biz-zle.github.io/donbosco/master-of-computer-science/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[dbths]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 16:35:31 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://biz-zle.github.io/donbosco/2021/09/19/master-of-computer-science/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Computer science is the study of algorithmic processes, computational machines, and computation itself. As a discipline, computer science spans a range of topics from theoretical studies of algorithms, computation, and information to the practical issues of implementing computational systems in hardware and software. Its [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p><strong>Computer science is the study of algorithmic processes, computational </strong>machines, and computation itself. As a discipline, computer science spans a range of topics from theoretical studies of algorithms, computation, and information to the practical issues of implementing computational systems in hardware and software.</p>



<p>Its fields can be divided into theoretical and practical disciplines. For example, the theory of computation concerns abstract models of computation and general classes of problems that can be solved using them, while computer graphics or computational geometry emphasize more specific applications. Algorithms and data structures have been called the heart of computer science. Programming language theory considers approaches to the description of computational processes, while computer programming involves the use of them to create complex systems. Computer architecture describes the construction of computer components and computer-operated equipment. Artificial intelligence aims to synthesize goal-orientated processes such as problem-solving, decision-making, environmental adaptation, planning, and learning found in humans and animals. A digital computer is capable of simulating various information processes. The fundamental concern of computer science is determining what can and cannot be automated. Computer scientists usually focus on academic research. The Turing Award is generally recognized as the highest distinction in computer sciences.</p>



<blockquote class="wp-block-quote"><p><em>he needs of a small-time tour operator are a lot different from the needs of a large international travel agency itself.</em></p><p><strong>Steve Doe –&nbsp;</strong>Partner</p></blockquote>



<hr class="wp-block-separator"/>



<p>Eventually, you must also offer them attractive and competitive tour packages. You must be able to clearly communicate to your customers what your services are, how they are different from others compelling manner.</p>



<p>Of course, you would want your visitors to conveniently reach out to you and contact you. You would want to display all the crucial information about your company, including a map that would show your visitors where exactly they will find you.</p>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading">Displaying Company Information</h5>



<p>Here are the major fear of rejection symptoms identified by psychologists:</p>



<ul><li>It’s all the better if you can accept payments online so that you can close the sales then and there.</li><li>It is much easier and convenient for your customers as well, and you too increase your chance of generating leads.</li><li>To make sure that your travel company website is compatible with some kind of online payment mechanism.</li><li>These will be crucial and highly beneficial for you later in the process.</li></ul>



<h1 class="wp-block-heading">H1: Reject the Fulfilling Prophecy</h1>



<p>This is my average total monthly spending from one year living in Seattle’s Capitol Hill, one year living in San Francisco’s Upper Haight, one year traveling to 20 countries, and one month at a hotel in Bali. It is much cheaper for me to travel. Since the majority of my costs are from trains and flights, it’s significantly cheaper if I stay in one place.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">H2:Focus On How You Want to Be</h2>



<p>This is my average total monthly spending from one year living in Seattle’s Capitol Hill, one year living in San Francisco’s Upper Haight, one year traveling to 20 countries, and one month at a hotel in Bali. It is much cheaper for me to travel. Since the majority of my costs are from trains and flights.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">H3: Construct a Narrative</h3>



<p>Instead of working during the daylight hours and pushing all my free time to the worst part of the day, I prefer to enjoy the days and work at night. I get out of bed faster when I’m excited to go out, and when I don’t have to commute there’s just more time in the day. I like to work 7 days a week with flexible hours so I can take a day off when I please or enjoy an empty movie theater at 2pm.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">H4: Tap Into Your Imagination</h4>



<p>I now have friends all over the world whose life experiences are very different than mine and bring fresh perspectives to my ideas. I’m learning about the real problems that affect the world on a global scale, which will make me.</p>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading">H5: Embrace Not Knowing</h5>



<p>There’s a growing community of “digital nomads” who live a location independent lifestyle. We’re software developers, designers, writers, journalists, engineers, and all sorts of people who share a passion for the work we do.</p>



<h6 class="wp-block-heading">H6: Remember You Will Survive</h6>



<p>Three years ago I was preparing to leave my job at Microsoft to move to San Francisco to start a startup. My friend asked me “but why do you need to be in San Francisco when you can work on a computer from anywhere?” His question made a lot of sense. As I thought about it more, I began to question my assumptions about a “normal life” which don’t make sense in our modern world.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://biz-zle.github.io/donbosco/master-of-computer-science/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Bachelor Of Fashion Designing</title>
		<link>https://biz-zle.github.io/donbosco/bachelor-of-fashion-designing/</link>
					<comments>https://biz-zle.github.io/donbosco/bachelor-of-fashion-designing/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[dbths]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 16:30:56 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://biz-zle.github.io/donbosco/2021/09/19/bachelor-of-fashion-designing/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[Fashion design is the art of applying design, aesthetics, clothing construction, and natural beauty to clothing and its accessories. It is influenced by culture and different trends and has varied over time and place. &#8220;A fashion designer creates [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>Fashion design is the art of applying design, aesthetics, clothing construction, and natural beauty to clothing and its accessories. It is influenced by culture and different trends and has varied over time and place. &#8220;A fashion designer creates clothing, including dresses, suits, pants, and skirts, and accessories like shoes and handbags, for consumers. He or she can specialize in clothing, accessory, or jewelry design, or may work in more than one of these areas.</p>



<p><strong>Fashion designers</strong> work in a variety of different ways in designing their pieces and accessories such as rings, bracelets and necklaces. Because of the time required to bring a garment onto the market, designers must at times anticipate changes to consumer desires. Fashion designers are responsible for creating looks for individual garments, involving shape, color, fabric, trimming, and more.  Fashion designers play a major role in our world. Their talent and vision play a big role on how people present themselves. They influence society and the way they choose to express themselves.</p>



<p>Designers conduct research on fashion trends and interpret them for their audience. Their specific designs are used by manufacturers. This is the essence of a designer&#8217;s role; however, there is variation within this that is determined by the buying and merchandising approach, and product quality; for example, budget retailers will use inexpensive fabrics to interpret trends, but high-end retailers will ensure that the best available fabrics are used.</p>



<p>Fashion designers attempt to design clothes that are functional as well as aesthetically pleasing. They consider who is likely to wear a garment and the situations in which it will be worn, and they work within a wide range of materials, colors, patterns, and styles. Though most clothing worn for everyday wear falls within a narrow range of conventional styles, unusual garments are usually sought for special occasions such as evening wear or party dresses.</p>



<p>Some clothes are made specifically for an individual, as in the case of haute couture or bespoke tailoring. Today, most clothing is designed for the mass market, especially casual and everyday wear are called ready-to-wear.</p>



<p>Eventually, you must also offer them attractive and competitive tour packages. You must be able to clearly communicate to your customers what your services are, how they are different from others compelling manner.</p>



<p>Of course, you would want your visitors to conveniently reach out to you and contact you. You would want to display all the crucial information about your company, including a map that would show your visitors where exactly they will find you.</p>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading">Displaying Company Information</h5>



<p>Here are the major fear of rejection symptoms identified by psychologists:</p>



<ul><li>It’s all the better if you can accept payments online so that you can close the sales then and there.</li><li>It is much easier and convenient for your customers as well, and you too increase your chance of generating leads.</li><li>To make sure that your travel company website is compatible with some kind of online payment mechanism.</li><li>These will be crucial and highly beneficial for you later in the process.</li></ul>



<h1 class="wp-block-heading">H1: Reject the Fulfilling Prophecy</h1>



<p>This is my average total monthly spending from one year living in Seattle’s Capitol Hill, one year living in San Francisco’s Upper Haight, one year traveling to 20 countries, and one month at a hotel in Bali. It is much cheaper for me to travel. Since the majority of my costs are from trains and flights, it’s significantly cheaper if I stay in one place.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">H2:Focus On How You Want to Be</h2>



<p>This is my average total monthly spending from one year living in Seattle’s Capitol Hill, one year living in San Francisco’s Upper Haight, one year traveling to 20 countries, and one month at a hotel in Bali. It is much cheaper for me to travel. Since the majority of my costs are from trains and flights.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">H3: Construct a Narrative</h3>



<p>Instead of working during the daylight hours and pushing all my free time to the worst part of the day, I prefer to enjoy the days and work at night. I get out of bed faster when I’m excited to go out, and when I don’t have to commute there’s just more time in the day. I like to work 7 days a week with flexible hours so I can take a day off when I please or enjoy an empty movie theater at 2pm.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">H4: Tap Into Your Imagination</h4>



<p>I now have friends all over the world whose life experiences are very different than mine and bring fresh perspectives to my ideas. I’m learning about the real problems that affect the world on a global scale, which will make me.</p>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading">H5: Embrace Not Knowing</h5>



<p>There’s a growing community of “digital nomads” who live a location independent lifestyle. We’re software developers, designers, writers, journalists, engineers, and all sorts of people who share a passion for the work we do.</p>



<h6 class="wp-block-heading">H6: Remember You Will Survive</h6>



<p>Three years ago I was preparing to leave my job at Microsoft to move to San Francisco to start a startup. My friend asked me “but why do you need to be in San Francisco when you can work on a computer from anywhere?” His question made a lot of sense. As I thought about it more, I began to question my assumptions about a “normal life” which don’t make sense in our modern world.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://biz-zle.github.io/donbosco/bachelor-of-fashion-designing/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
		<item>
		<title>Master Of Business Administration</title>
		<link>https://biz-zle.github.io/donbosco/master-of-businessadministration/</link>
					<comments>https://biz-zle.github.io/donbosco/master-of-businessadministration/#respond</comments>
		
		<dc:creator><![CDATA[dbths]]></dc:creator>
		<pubDate>Sun, 19 Sep 2021 16:26:16 +0000</pubDate>
				<category><![CDATA[Business]]></category>
		<category><![CDATA[Education]]></category>
		<guid isPermaLink="false">https://biz-zle.github.io/donbosco/2021/09/19/master-of-businessadministration/</guid>

					<description><![CDATA[A Master of Business Administration (MBA; also Master&#8217;s in Business Administration) is a graduate degree focusing on business administration and investment management.The core courses in an MBA program cover various areas of business administration such as accounting, applied statistics, human resources, business [&#8230;]]]></description>
										<content:encoded><![CDATA[
<p>A Master of Business Administration (MBA; also Master&#8217;s in Business Administration) is a graduate degree focusing on business administration and investment management.The core courses in an MBA program cover various areas of business administration such as accounting, applied statistics, human resources, business communication, business ethics economics, management, entrepreneurship, marketing, supply-chain management, and operations management in a manner most relevant to management analysis and strategy. It originated in the United States in the early 20th century when the country industrialized and companies</p>



<p>Most programs also include elective courses and concentrations for further study in a particular area, for example, accounting, finance, marketing, and human resources. MBA programs in the United States typically require completing about forty to sixty credits (sixty to ninety in a quarter system), much higher than the thirty credits (thirty-six to forty-five in a quarter system) typically required for degrees that cover some of the same material such as the Master of Economics, Master of Finance, Master of Accountancy, Master of Science in Marketing and Master of Science in Management.</p>



<p>The MBA is a terminal degree and a professional degree. Accreditation bodies specifically for MBA programs ensure consistency and quality of education. Business schools in many countries offer programs tailored to the full-time, part-time, executive (abridged coursework typically occurring on nights or weekends), and distance learning students, many with specialized concentrations.</p>



<p>Eventually, you must also offer them attractive and competitive tour packages. You must be able to clearly communicate to your customers what your services are, how they are different from others compelling manner.</p>



<p>Of course, you would want your visitors to conveniently reach out to you and contact you. You would want to display all the crucial information about your company, including a map that would show your visitors where exactly they will find you.</p>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading">Displaying Company Information</h5>



<p>Here are the major fear of rejection symptoms identified by psychologists:</p>



<ul><li>It’s all the better if you can accept payments online so that you can close the sales then and there.</li><li>It is much easier and convenient for your customers as well, and you too increase your chance of generating leads.</li><li>To make sure that your travel company website is compatible with some kind of online payment mechanism.</li><li>These will be crucial and highly beneficial for you later in the process.</li></ul>



<h1 class="wp-block-heading">H1: Reject the Fulfilling Prophecy</h1>



<p>This is my average total monthly spending from one year living in Seattle’s Capitol Hill, one year living in San Francisco’s Upper Haight, one year traveling to 20 countries, and one month at a hotel in Bali. It is much cheaper for me to travel. Since the majority of my costs are from trains and flights, it’s significantly cheaper if I stay in one place.</p>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">H2:Focus On How You Want to Be</h2>



<p>This is my average total monthly spending from one year living in Seattle’s Capitol Hill, one year living in San Francisco’s Upper Haight, one year traveling to 20 countries, and one month at a hotel in Bali. It is much cheaper for me to travel. Since the majority of my costs are from trains and flights.</p>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">H3: Construct a Narrative</h3>



<p>Instead of working during the daylight hours and pushing all my free time to the worst part of the day, I prefer to enjoy the days and work at night. I get out of bed faster when I’m excited to go out, and when I don’t have to commute there’s just more time in the day. I like to work 7 days a week with flexible hours so I can take a day off when I please or enjoy an empty movie theater at 2pm.</p>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">H4: Tap Into Your Imagination</h4>



<p>I now have friends all over the world whose life experiences are very different than mine and bring fresh perspectives to my ideas. I’m learning about the real problems that affect the world on a global scale, which will make me.</p>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading">H5: Embrace Not Knowing</h5>



<p>There’s a growing community of “digital nomads” who live a location independent lifestyle. We’re software developers, designers, writers, journalists, engineers, and all sorts of people who share a passion for the work we do.</p>



<h6 class="wp-block-heading">H6: Remember You Will Survive</h6>



<p>Three years ago I was preparing to leave my job at Microsoft to move to San Francisco to start a startup. My friend asked me “but why do you need to be in San Francisco when you can work on a computer from anywhere?” His question made a lot of sense. As I thought about it more, I began to question my assumptions about a “normal life” which don’t make sense in our modern world.</p>



<h1 class="wp-block-heading">H1: Heading 1</h1>



<h2 class="wp-block-heading">H2: Heading 2</h2>



<h3 class="wp-block-heading">H3: Heading 3</h3>



<h4 class="wp-block-heading">H4: Heading 4</h4>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading">H5: Heading 5</h5>



<h6 class="wp-block-heading">H6: Heading 6</h6>



<p>Three years ago I was preparing to leave my job at Microsoft to move to San Francisco to start a startup. My friend asked me “but why do you need to be in San Francisco when you can work on a computer from anywhere?” His question made a lot of sense. As I thought about it more, I began to question my assumptions about a “normal life” which don’t make sense in our modern world.</p>



<h5 class="wp-block-heading">Displaying Company Information</h5>



<p>Here are the major fear of rejection symptoms identified by psychologists:</p>



<ul><li>It’s all the better if you can accept payments online so that you can close the sales then and there.</li><li>It is much easier and convenient for your customers as well, and you too increase your chance of generating leads.</li><li>To make sure that your travel company website is compatible with some kind of online payment mechanism.</li><li>These will be crucial and highly beneficial for you later in the process.</li></ul>



<p>Three years ago I was preparing to leave my job at Microsoft to move to San Francisco to start a startup. My friend asked me “but why do you need to be in San Francisco when you can work on a computer from anywhere?” His question made a lot of sense. As I thought about it more, I began to question my assumptions about a “normal life” which don’t make sense in our modern world.</p>
]]></content:encoded>
					
					<wfw:commentRss>https://biz-zle.github.io/donbosco/master-of-businessadministration/feed/</wfw:commentRss>
			<slash:comments>0</slash:comments>
		
		
			</item>
	</channel>
</rss>
